{
	"questions":[
		{"question":"The average of first 50 natural numbers is …………?", "a":"25.30", "b":"25.5", "c":"25.00", "d":"12.25", "ans":"b"},
		{"question":"A fraction which bears the same ratio to 1/27 as 3/11 bear to 5/9 is equal to ", "a":"1/55", "b":"55", "c":"3/11", "d":"1/11", "ans":"a"},
		{"question":"The number of 3-digit numbers divisible by 6, is …………?", "a":"149", "b":"166", "c":"150", "d":"151", "ans":"c"},
		{"question":"What is 1004 divided by 2?", "a":"52", "b":"502", "c":"520", "d":"5002", "ans":"b"},
		{"question":"A clock strikes once at 1 o’clock, twice at 2 o’clock, thrice at 3 o’clock and so on. How many times will it strike in 24 hours?", "a":"78", "b":"136", "c":"156", "d":"196", "ans":"c"},
		{"question":"125 gallons of a mixture contains 20% water. What amount of additional water should be added such that water content be raised to 25%?", "a":"15/2 gallons.", "b":"17/2 gallons.", "c":"19/2 gallons.", "d":"81/3 gallons.", "ans":"c"},
		{"question":"106 × 106 – 94 × 94 = ?", "a":"2004", "b":"2400", "c":"1904", "d":"1906", "ans":"b"},
		{"question":"Which of the following numbers gives 240 when added to its own square?", "a":"15", "b":"16", "c":"18", "d":"20", "ans":"a"},
		{"question":"Evaluation of 83 × 82 × 8-5 is …………?", "a":"1", "b":"0", "c":"8", "d":"None of these", "ans":"a"},
		{"question":"The simplest form of 1.5 : 2.5 is …………… ", "a":"6 : 10", "b":"15 : 25", "c":"0.75 : 1.25", "d":"3 : 5", "ans":"d"}
	]
}